1. comment("Story: Book an appointment")
5. comment("Given that the user has logged into their account")
9. openBrowser(G_SiteURL)
13. callTestCase(findTestCase("Common Test Cases/Login"), ["Username":"John Doe", "Password":"ThisIsNotAPassword"], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Page_CuraHomepage/btn_MakeAppointment"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_UserName"), Username)
9. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_Password"), Password)
13. click(findTestObject("Page_Login/btn_Login"))
17. landingPage = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/div_Appointment"), G_Timeout)
17. comment("And Appointment page is displayed")
21. if (true)
1. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/lst_Facility"), "Hongkong CURA Healthcare Center", false)
5. check(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/chk_Medicaid"))
9. check(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/chk_Readmission"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/txt_VisitDate"), "27/12/2016")
17. setText(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/txt_Comment"), "Please make appointment as soon as possible.")
25. comment("When he fills in valid information in Appointment page")
29. click(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/btn_BookAppointment"))
33. verifyTextPresent("Appointment Confirmation", false)
37. comment("Then he should be able to book a new appointment")
41. if (true)
1. verifyMatch("Hongkong CURA Healthcare Center", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_Facility")), false)
5. verifyMatch("Yes", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_HospitalReadmission")), false)
9. verifyMatch("Medicaid", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_Program")), false)
13. verifyMatch("27/12/2016", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_VisitDate")), false)
17. verifyMatch("Please make appointment as soon as possible.", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_Comment")), false)
45. takeScreenshot()
49. closeBrowser()